_ is a slippery slope that leads to _.{p2}
_. Betcha can't have just one!
_. High five, bro.
_. Its a trap!
_. That's how I want to die.
_: good to the last drop.
_: kid-tested, mother-approved.
_+_ = _.{d2}{p3}
A romantic candlelit dinner would be incomplete without _.
After the earthquake, Sean Penn brought _ to the people of Haiti.
Alternative medicine is now embracing the curative powers of _.
And the Academy Award for _ goes to_.{p2}
BILLY MAYS HERE FOR _.
But before I kill you, Mr. Bond, I must show you _.
Coming to Broadway this season _: The Musical.
Daddy, why is mommy crying?
Dear Abby,[LINE]I'm having some trouble with _ and would like your advice.
During his childhood, Salvador Dal\u00ED produced hundreds of paintings of _.
During sex, I like to think about _.
For my next trick, I will pull _ out of _.{p2}
Here is the church \ Here is the Steeple \ Open the doors \ And there Is  _.
How am I maintaining my relationship status?
How did I lose my virginity?
I do not know with what weapons World War III will be fought, but World War IV will be fought with _.
I drink to forget _.
I got 99 problems but _ ain't one.
I never truly understood _ until I encountered _.{p2}
I'm sorry Professor, but I couldn't complete my homework because of _.
In 1,000 years, when paper money is a distant memory, how will we pay for goods and services.
In a world ravaged by _, our only solace is _.{p2}
In L.A. County Jail, word is you can trade 200 cigarettes for _.
In M. Night Shymalan's new movie, Bruce Willis discovers that _ had really been _ all along.{p2}
In Michael Jackson's final moments, he thought about _.
In the new Disney Channel Original Movie, Hannah Montana struggles with _ for the first time.
Instead of coal, Santa now gives bad children _.
It's a pity that kids these days are getting involved with _.
Life for American Indians was forever changed when the White Man introduced them to _.
Lifetime\u00AE presents _, the story of _.{p2}
Major League Baseball has banned _ for giving players an unfair advantage.
Make a haiku.{d2}{p3}
Maybe she's born with it. Maybe it's _.
MTV's new reality show features eight washed-up celebrities living with _.
Next from J.K. Rowling: Harry Potter and the Chamber of _.
Next on ESPN2, the World Series of _.
Rumor has it that Vladmir Putin's favorite delicacy is _ stuffed with _.{p2}
Step 1: _. Step 2: _. Step 3: Profit.{p2}
Studies show that lab rats navigate mazes 50% faster after being exposed to _.
That's right, I killed _.How, you ask? _.{p2}
The class field trip was completely ruined by _.
The Smithsonian Museum of Natural History has just opened an interactive exhibit on _.
This is the way the world ends \ This is the way the world ends \ Not with a bang but with _.
TSA guidelines now prohibit _ on airplanes.
War![LINE]What is it good for?
What am I giving up for Lent?
What are my parents hiding from me?
What did I bring back from Mexico?
What did the U.S. airdrop to the children of Afghanistan?
What did Vin Diesel eat for dinner?
What do old people smell like?
What does Dick Cheney prefer?
What don't you want to find in your Kung Pao chicken.
What ended my last relationship?
What gets better with age?
What gives me uncontrollable gas?
What helps Obama unwind?
What is Batman's guilty pleasure?
What never fails to liven up the party?
What will always get you laid?
What will I bring back in time to convince people that I am a powerful wizard?
What would grandma find disturbing, yet oddly charming?
What's a girl's best friend?
What's my anti-drug?
What's my secret power?
What's Teach for America using to inspire inner city students to succeed?
What's that smell?
What's that sound?
What's the most emo?
What's the new fad diet?
What's the next Happy Meal\u00AE toy?
What's the next superhero/sidekick duo?{p2}
What's there a tone of in heaven?
When I am a billionaire, I shall erect a 50-foot statue to commemorate _.
When I am President of the United States I will create the Department of _.
When I was tripping on acid _ turned into _.{p2}
When Pharoah remained unmoved, Moses called down a Plague of _.
While the United States raced the Soviet Union to the moon, the Mexican government funneled millions of pesos into research on _.
White people like _.
Why am I sticky?
Why can't I sleep at night?
Why do I hurt all over?
